[{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664591646,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"144","question":"Describe the funniest thing that ever happened to you.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":5888,"timeElapsed":323705},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664596150,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"144","question":"Describe the funniest thing that ever happened to you.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":4499,"timeElapsed":328210},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664601254,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"144","question":"Describe the funniest thing that ever happened to you.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":5098,"timeElapsed":333314},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664608733,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"144","question":"Describe the funniest thing that ever happened to you.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":7475,"timeElapsed":340793},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664616733,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"144","question":"Describe the funniest thing that ever happened to you.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":7994,"timeElapsed":348793},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664625460,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"144","question":"Describe the funniest thing that ever happened to you.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":8721,"timeElapsed":357520},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664629827,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"144","question":"Describe the funniest thing that ever happened to you.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":4362,"timeElapsed":361887},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664636873,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"144","question":"Describe the funniest thing that ever happened to you.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":7040,"timeElapsed":368933},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664641147,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"144","question":"Describe the funniest thing that ever happened to you.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":4269,"timeElapsed":373207},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664650629,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":7624,"timeElapsed":382689},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664654655,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":4019,"timeElapsed":386714},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664657127,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":2467,"timeElapsed":389187},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664662460,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":5325,"timeElapsed":394519},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664665336,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":2872,"timeElapsed":397396},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664670813,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":5472,"timeElapsed":402873},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664675783,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":4964,"timeElapsed":407843},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664680001,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":4213,"timeElapsed":412061},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664682770,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2764,"timeElapsed":414830},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664692101,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":7478,"timeElapsed":424161},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664694902,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":2795,"timeElapsed":426961},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664697969,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3063,"timeElapsed":430029},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664704375,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":6398,"timeElapsed":436435},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664707175,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":2794,"timeElapsed":439235},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664710961,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":3781,"timeElapsed":443021},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664714050,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":3083,"timeElapsed":446110},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664718358,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":4303,"timeElapsed":450418},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664720575,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":2213,"timeElapsed":452634},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664728437,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"51","question":"Do you think people can change fundamental things about who they are? If so, what kinds of things? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":6248,"timeElapsed":460496},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664731227,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"51","question":"Do you think people can change fundamental things about who they are? If so, what kinds of things? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":2787,"timeElapsed":463287},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664734757,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"51","question":"Do you think people can change fundamental things about who they are? If so, what kinds of things? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":3524,"timeElapsed":466817},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664739205,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"51","question":"Do you think people can change fundamental things about who they are? If so, what kinds of things? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":4443,"timeElapsed":471265},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664742207,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"51","question":"Do you think people can change fundamental things about who they are? If so, what kinds of things? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":2998,"timeElapsed":474266},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664748507,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"51","question":"Do you think people can change fundamental things about who they are? If so, what kinds of things? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":6294,"timeElapsed":480567},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664751859,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"51","question":"Do you think people can change fundamental things about who they are? If so, what kinds of things? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":3346,"timeElapsed":483919},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664755521,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"51","question":"Do you think people can change fundamental things about who they are? If so, what kinds of things? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":3654,"timeElapsed":487580},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664757828,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"51","question":"Do you think people can change fundamental things about who they are? If so, what kinds of things? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":2301,"timeElapsed":489888},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664771590,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":10123,"timeElapsed":503650},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664774407,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":2815,"timeElapsed":506467},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664777758,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":3347,"timeElapsed":509818},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664782239,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":4475,"timeElapsed":514299},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664784702,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2459,"timeElapsed":516762},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664788286,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":3578,"timeElapsed":520345},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664791754,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":3463,"timeElapsed":523814},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664799176,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":7413,"timeElapsed":531236},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664802374,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":3194,"timeElapsed":534434},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664826225,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":22072,"timeElapsed":558285},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664830361,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":4131,"timeElapsed":562419},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664832764,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":2398,"timeElapsed":564823},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664836834,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":4064,"timeElapsed":568894},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664839524,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":2683,"timeElapsed":571584},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664847138,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":7608,"timeElapsed":579198},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664850855,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3712,"timeElapsed":582915},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664854813,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3953,"timeElapsed":586872},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664859601,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":4782,"timeElapsed":591660},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664861997,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":2391,"timeElapsed":594057},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664871049,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"208","question":"Do you consider yourself more of a “cat person” or a “dog person”? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":5858,"timeElapsed":603109},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664874160,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"208","question":"Do you consider yourself more of a “cat person” or a “dog person”? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":3105,"timeElapsed":606220},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664877983,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"208","question":"Do you consider yourself more of a “cat person” or a “dog person”? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":3817,"timeElapsed":610043},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664880829,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"208","question":"Do you consider yourself more of a “cat person” or a “dog person”? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":2841,"timeElapsed":612889},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664883700,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"208","question":"Do you consider yourself more of a “cat person” or a “dog person”? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":2866,"timeElapsed":615760},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664887394,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"208","question":"Do you consider yourself more of a “cat person” or a “dog person”? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":3687,"timeElapsed":619454},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664889890,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"208","question":"Do you consider yourself more of a “cat person” or a “dog person”? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":2491,"timeElapsed":621950},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664893190,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"208","question":"Do you consider yourself more of a “cat person” or a “dog person”? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":3292,"timeElapsed":625249},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664895507,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"208","question":"Do you consider yourself more of a “cat person” or a “dog person”? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":2312,"timeElapsed":627567},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664944719,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":47417,"timeElapsed":676779},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664947117,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":2392,"timeElapsed":679177},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664976297,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":29174,"timeElapsed":708357},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664985560,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":9259,"timeElapsed":717620},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664988023,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":2456,"timeElapsed":720083},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664991076,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":3046,"timeElapsed":723135},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664993954,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":2873,"timeElapsed":726013},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664997705,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":3747,"timeElapsed":729765},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665000182,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":2472,"timeElapsed":732242},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665008928,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":6834,"timeElapsed":740988},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665012162,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":3226,"timeElapsed":744221},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665014833,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":2667,"timeElapsed":746893},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665018703,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":3864,"timeElapsed":750762},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665021449,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2741,"timeElapsed":753509},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665024602,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":3147,"timeElapsed":756662},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665027354,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":2745,"timeElapsed":759414},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665038323,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":10963,"timeElapsed":770381},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665043160,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":4828,"timeElapsed":775219},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665047075,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":3911,"timeElapsed":779134},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665053782,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":4576,"timeElapsed":785841},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665057378,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":3591,"timeElapsed":789437},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665060404,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":3022,"timeElapsed":792464},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665064469,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":4059,"timeElapsed":796529},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665067298,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":2824,"timeElapsed":799358},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665070831,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":3528,"timeElapsed":802891},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665073481,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":2644,"timeElapsed":805541},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665077476,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":3991,"timeElapsed":809536},{"subjectID":"4b2xyossdl","prolificID":"666b254d9bc6d71a71b89cee","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215f94eeb8f1992fc68c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665080937,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":3456,"timeElapsed":812997}]